[
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "0",
        "response": "0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 1,
        "label_": "0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "1",
        "response": "0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "2",
        "response": "0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "3",
        "response": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "4",
        "response": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "5",
        "response": "0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "6",
        "response": "0,0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "7",
        "response": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "8",
        "response": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "9",
        "response": "0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "10",
        "response": "0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,0,0,0,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "11",
        "response": "4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,4,0,0\n\ninput 2: 8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "12",
        "response": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "13",
        "response": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "14",
        "response": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "15",
        "response": "0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "16",
        "response": "0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,8,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,2,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "17",
        "response": "0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "18",
        "response": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0"
    },
    {
        "label": "0,0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "prompt": "input 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 1: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,6,6,6,6,6,6,0,0,0\n\ninput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 2: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 3: 0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,7,0,0,0,0,0,0\n\ninput 4: 0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0\noutput 4: ",
        "task_name": "19",
        "response": "0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0",
        "eval": 0,
        "label_": "0,0,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,5,0,0,0,0,0,0"
    }
]